"When she locks eyes with another,
“那個能力就是在互相對望時
only then can she hear the voice in their heart."
她可以聽到對方的心聲
"One day, the girl met a boy with a kind heart."
有天少女遇見了少年 他擁有一顆溫柔的心
"The boy showed a great amount of love to the girl."
少年向少女傳達了許多愛意”
"However, the girl kept her power to hear people's hearts
“但是這名少女並未將擁有 能聽到心聲能力的事
as a secret from the boy."
告訴少年
"In the end, the two of them
在最後有各種不幸
were met with much misfortune."
發生在兩人身上”
Misfortune…
不幸…
"That was the fate given to the girl who could hear
“對於能聽見心聲的少女
people's hearts."
這便是上天賦予她的命運”
What is this?
這是怎麼回事？
I'm home, Yuri.
我回來了，侑里小姐
-Welcome back. -Hungry, right?
-回來啦 -你餓了吧？
I'll cook now.
我來做飯
By the way, Tae-o…
我問你喔，泰晤…
Um…
那個…
What is it?
怎麼了？
It's nothing.
不，沒什麼
Don't worry.
別擔心
Just five minutes.
給我五分鐘就好
THE GIRL WHO CAN HEAR YOUR HEART
（能聽見你心聲的少女）
KOREAN CHILDREN'S BOOK
（韓文童書 《能聽見你心聲的少女》）
AUTHOR: MIN HA-NA
（作者名：閔荷娜）
OUT OF PRINT
（絕版，不再發行）
"Out of print."
“絕版”
Misfortune.
不幸
"That was the fate given."
被賦予的命運
Is it just a coincidence?
只是巧合嗎？
No, but…
不，但是…
Hm?
嗯？
Come in. Do you copy? Mahiro, reporting in.
收到請回答，我是真尋
Can you hear me, Yuri?
侑里小姐，你有聽到嗎？
I want you to try the samples I made for the new summer product.
夏季新商品的試作品已經完成了 待會想麻煩你試吃
Whoa, you actually heard me.
天啊，真的能溝通耶
Oh, and how about we get some lunch soon?
對了，是不是差不多該吃午餐了？
A new bakery opened up nearby.
附近開了一家新的麵包店喔
Yuri, you seem kind of down today.
侑里小姐，你感覺沒什麼精神呢
Something wrong?
發生了什麼事嗎？
What is she doing?
她這是在做什麼啊？
Let me get this straight.
先來整理一下狀況
Basically, a picture book written about the same power as yours
也就是說，泰晤不知為何有一本繪本
is in Tae-o's possession.
裡面提及和侑里小姐相同的能力
Yeah.
對
And coincidentally, that story
而且很巧的是裡面的故事
is linked to the memories you made together for some reason.
能聯想到你們兩人的戀愛回憶
Yeah, seems like that.
是啊，沒錯
To add to the mystery, Tae-o somehow has
然後更加不可思議的是 泰晤出於某種理由
a business card from Min Ha-na, the author.
擁有作者閔荷娜的名片
What do you think? Is it just a coincidence?
你覺得呢？感覺不像是巧合
It's all way too connected.
不太可能這麼湊巧吧
Right?
說得也是
I'm so confused.
我都被搞糊塗了
There's more to that book, right?
這個故事還有後續對吧？
Yeah.
對
Maybe I'll understand if I read the whole thing.
讀完就會知道是怎麼一回事了嗎？
No, there's no way.
不，還是不可能
I'm sure it's a coincidence. You're worrying too much.
一定是剛好啦，你想太多了
You're right.
你說得對
TAE-O'S PICTURE BOOK
（泰晤的繪本）
MUCH MISFORTUNE PICTURE OF THUNDER, TURTLE, PAPER SLIPS
（各種不幸 雷電、烏龜、紙鈔的畫）
Is this…
這會是…
true?
真的嗎？
What happened?
你怎麼了？
Kame…
龜哥
The thunder…
打雷了…
Ouch!
好痛…
-Kame, are you okay? -That hurts!
-龜哥，你沒事吧？ -好痛…
He got scared by the thunder just now and threw his back out.
他好像是被剛剛那道雷嚇到 所以閃到腰了
What?
不會吧
-Please get up. -I don't think I can.
-總之先起來再說吧 -可能起不來了
-That hurts! -Thunder. Turtle.
-痛死啦… -雷電、烏龜
-Yuri! -Huh?
-侑里小姐！ -幹嘛？
Turtle! Thunder!
烏龜！雷電！
-"Kame" means turtle! -Huh?
-“烏龜”就是他啊！ -什麼？
Come on, the turtle and thunder!
所以說是烏龜跟雷電啊！
From the picture book!
就如繪本裡畫的！
Kame?
烏龜？
-Kame! Get up! -Don't hit me!
-龜哥！振作起來啊！ -別打啦，好疼！
That picture book isn't a coincidence.
那繪本的內容不是巧合
What?
不會吧？
Yuri, leave this to me.
侑里小姐，這件事就交給我吧
Huh?
嗯？
I have a plan.
我有個主意
Can't you just speak out loud?
直接用嘴巴說不就好了？
I, the chocolatier, will solve this mystery.
就由我這個巧克力師傅 來解開此謎團吧
Let's solve the mystery after chocolate.
推理要在吃完巧克力之後
Coming.
來了
Hello.
你好
Annyeonghaseyo. Sorry for coming along too.
“你好啊”
It's okay.
沒關係
Yuri told me. Come in.
侑里小姐有跟我說，請進
Thank you. Don't mind if I do.
謝謝，打擾啦
Sorry about this.
總覺得很不好意思
It's fine.
沒關係
I'm happy to host.
我很開心
Food tastes better when you share it.
大家一起吃飯才好吃嘛
-Come in. -Thank you.
-進來吧 -打擾了
This must be it.
就是這本啊
Oh, are you hungry?
啊，肚子餓了嗎？
No worries. I've already prepared the food.
別擔心，飯已經做好了
Please.
請坐
Sit tight for a moment.
你就坐下來等一下吧
Come in. Do you copy? Mahiro, reporting in.
收到請回答，我是真尋
Can you hear me?
有聽到嗎？
No, use the signal we agreed on.
不對啦，要用該才說好的暗號
All right, let's run through it.
好，那來確認流程
I'll lure away Tae-o now, and you'll use that time to read the book.
接下來我會把泰晤帶出去
Okay?
可以嗎？
All right.
好
Hey, oppa.
我說啊，oppa
Want to come to the convenience store with me? I forgot to buy alcohol.
我們去便利商店好不好？我忘了買酒
I'm not your oppa.
我不是你的“oppa”耶
It's fine. Come on, let's go, oppa.
怎樣都好啦，我們走吧，oppa
It's not fine.
不好
And I have a ton of alcohol.
而且我這裡有很多酒
I'm feeling like wine tonight.
我今天想喝紅酒啦
Wine? With Korean food?
紅酒？配韓式料理？
Jeez, let's just go, oppa.
真是的，總之我們走，oppa
Now's your chance.
就是現在
We'll be back!
我們走囉！
See you soon.
路上小心
Hurry up.
快點…
Senpai, you're finally here.
學長，你終於來啦
Why? Why is he here?
怎麼會？為何你會來？
He's trying to come in!
而且還要進去！
Wait, you can't!
等等，不行！
Hello.
你好
Why is Onoda here?
話說為什麼小野田先生會來啊？
I invited him.
是我請他來的
Food tastes better when you share it.
大家一起吃飯比較好吃啊
-Come in. -Thanks.
-請進 -謝謝
Don't mind if I do.
打擾了
Like I said, that's incorrect.
所以我說了不是
I'm not your oppa.
我不是你的“oppa”
But oppa means "big brother," right?
但“oppa”不就是“哥”的意思嗎？
From what I remember, women in Korea use oppa to refer to older men, right?
在韓國女性好像會用“oppa” 來稱呼年長的男性對吧？
Yes, but Mahiro is older than me.
沒錯，但是真尋小姐的年紀比我大
What's the big deal? Just let me call you oppa.
有什麼關係？ 我就想叫“oppa”，讓我叫啦
No, absolutely not.
不，絕對不行
You're such a stickler.
什麼嘛，小氣鬼
Oppa.
oppa…
Hm, this wine is nice.
嗯，這紅酒好好喝
That's great.
太好了
Mahiro was just saying how she wanted to drink wine.
剛好真尋小姐想喝紅酒
-Really? -Huh?
-是這樣嗎？ -什麼？
Yes, I guess.
是啊
Do you like wine?
你喜歡紅酒嗎？
Well, when I'm in the mood for it.
這個嘛，還算喜歡吧
Her favorite alcoholic drink is wine.
她喜歡的酒是紅酒
What region?
產地呢？
What?
什麼？
How often do you drink?
請告訴我你喝酒的頻率
Do you have a high or low tolerance?
你酒量好不好？
What kind of drunk are you, and how do I take care of you?
喝多時會出現什麼樣的行為模式 又該如何應對？
-And-- -H-hold on.
-還有… -你等一下
What are you doing?
為什麼要問這些？
I want to do research
我想好好研究…
about you, Mahiro.
真尋小姐
What?
什麼意思？
Research?
研究？
I don't quite understand.
我不太懂你的意思
I apologize.
不好意思
But…
可是…
This is the only way I'll know.
如果我什麼都不知道就不會懂
I want to reconsider this again once I get to know you properly.
我想好好認識你 在徹底理解後再做一次驗證
In my life,
我想知道你的存在
what role
在我的人生中
does your existence play?
會帶來怎麼樣的效應
Huh?
什麼？
Now I see.
原來是這樣啊
Yuri.
侑里小姐
Let's go buy some ice cream.
我們去買冰吧
Right now?
現在嗎？
Yes, now.
就是現在
Wait, but, um…
等等，可是那個…
Hurry, let's go.
快點，我們走吧
What? But…
什麼？但是我…
Yuri, we have to be considerate here.
侑里小姐，現在要懂得察言觀色啊
Considerate?
察言觀色？
Watch your feet.
小心腳下喔
May I…
我可以繼續…
continue with my questions?
向你提問嗎？
Yes.
可以
Yuri.
侑里小姐
Are you a bit cold, by chance?
那個，你是不是覺得有點冷？
Oh, just a bit.
是啊，有一點冷
That's no good.
那可不行
Your hands are cold.
你的手好冰
It's not a big deal.
你太誇張了啦
Not yet.
不行
They're still cold.
還很冷
Tae-o.
泰晤
-Actually… -Yuri.
-其實… -侑里小姐
Close your eyes.
把眼睛閉起來
So adorable.
真美啊
Do you feel warm now?
這樣有變暖了嗎？
Thanks, are these meat buns?
謝謝，是肉包嗎？
No, they are not meat buns.
不對，不是肉包
Well, then.
那麼…
It's time
我現在呢
for a quiz.
要出題了
Okay.
好
What's in here?
這裡面是什麼？
Um…
我想想…
If they're not meat buns, are they red bean buns?
不是肉包的話，是豆沙包之類的嗎？
Was I right or wrong?
是對還是錯？
You were wrong.
答錯了
Then… curry buns.
這樣啊，那是咖哩包嗎？
-No. -Pizza buns.
-不對… -披薩包
What else could they be?
還有什麼其他口味啊？
Here's a hint, just for you.
我特別給你一個提示
Give it a taste.
吃吃看
Thanks for the food.
那就不客氣了
Is this crab?
這是螃蟹？
Ding, ding! That's correct.
叮咚噹！答對了
It's my favorite. Crab buns.
這是我最愛的蟹肉包
You like crab buns, Tae-o?
原來你喜歡蟹肉包啊？
I didn't know.
我之前都不知道
Seeing Mahiro and Onoda earlier got me thinking that
剛才看到真尋他們的樣子讓我覺得
there's still so much I don't know about you, Tae-o.
你還有好多事情是我不知道的
Yuri,
侑里小姐
what is your favorite food?
你最喜歡的料理是什麼？
My favorite?
最喜歡的嗎？
Omurice, I think.
應該是蛋包飯
Omurice?
蛋包飯？
My father was a chef,
我爸爸以前是廚師
so he would often make it for me at the restaurant.
小時候他常在店裡做給我吃
Oh, also,
對了，還有喔
I like coffee and chocolate.
那就是咖啡跟巧克力
He would always give me some with my food.
他以前總是會跟料理一起拿給我吃
So that's why our company makes chocolate and coffee.
所以我們公司的商品 才是巧克力和咖啡啊
Yeah.
對
But, well,
不過呢
my father has never had the chance to drink our coffee.
我爸爸沒喝過我們公司的咖啡就是了
There's a lot for me too.
我也一樣
There is still a lot I don't know about you, Yuri.
關於你，還有很多我不知道的事
That's why
所以我啊
I want to learn more.
想要更了解你這個人
But…
可是…
even if I don't know, my feelings are still the same.
就算不知道，我對你的感情也不會變
Your kind side.
不管是溫柔的你
Your angry side.
還是生氣的你
Every side of you.
無論是怎樣的你
I love them all very much.
都是我最喜歡的侑里小姐
That's why
所以說啊
I am incredibly happy right now.
我現在非常幸福
Me too.
我也是
Thank you.
謝謝你
Shall we head back now?
差不多該回去了吧？
Yes.
好
I'm headed this way.
那我走這邊
You're not walking me back?
不送我回去啊？
Mahiro.
真尋小姐
I'll contact you.
我會再跟你聯絡
Huh?
什麼？
I still have more questions.
因為我還有問題要問你
I'll send you a list later.
我之後會整理成清單傳給你
Goodbye then.
再見
Onoda is a bit eccentric,
小野田先生雖然有些奇特
but he's giving you some serious thought.
但感覺他在認真考慮你的事
Do you think so?
是這樣嗎？
I feel more like I'm a research subject
與其說他是把我視為戀愛對象
than a romantic interest.
還比較像是研究對象呢
Oh, that's right. I read the picture book.
對了，侑里小姐，我讀了那繪本
What? You really read it?
什麼？你真的成功看到了？
When Onoda was busy calculating what my alcohol limit is,
我趁小野田先生在計算 我的適當酒精攝取量的時候
I read the next two pages.
有往下讀，雖然只有兩頁啦
I even took photos.
還拍了照片
Thank you.
謝謝
What did it say?
裡面寫了什麼？
Well…
上面寫著…
If there were a way
如果能消除
to get rid of that power…
那種能力…
would you want to?
你會想消除嗎？
"The girl said to the god,
“少女問了神
'Tell me how to get rid of this power.'"
‘請告訴我消除這個能力的方法’
"Then, the god told her how."
結果神跟她說的方法
"She must…"
就是…”
LOCK EYES WITH THE ONE SHE LOVES FOR 33 SECONDS
（和心愛的人對視33秒）
It never even crossed my mind.
我從來就沒想過
If I could get rid of this power…
如果能消除這能力的話…
I am incredibly happy right now.
我現在非常幸福
…both my love and I
也許就能和心愛的人
can gaze upon each other like this forever.
四目交接到永遠
But…
但是…
if I lose this power…
如果我失去了這個能力…
Dad and I…
我和爸爸…
can never talk to each other again.
就再也無法對話了
What's most important to me?
對我而言最重要的東西是什麼？
BUT IF YOU DO NOT HURRY, YOU WILL LOSE WHAT'S MOST IMPORTANT TO YOU
（但要抓緊時間，若不快點決定 將會失去你“最重要的東西”）
Yes?
是
Yuri, I'm coming in.
侑里小姐，打擾了
I'd be torn too
你一定很煩惱
about whether to keep that power or not.
是否要消除那個能力
Yeah, it's a hard choice to make.
是啊，沒辦法如此簡單地做出決定
But if you don't hurry, something bad might happen.
但不快點決定的話 或許會發生什麼糟糕的事
But it's just a picture book.
不過說起來那只是一本繪本
Who knows if it's true or not?
也不知道是真是假
-Boss! -Yes?
-社長！ -是！
This is horrible!
大事不好了！
-Ouch! -Hey!
-好痛… -小心點…
-Are you okay? -Venture Capital Partners,
-你沒事吧？ -夥伴創投…
the very important VCP, has gone bankrupt!
那個VCP陷入經營危機！
-What?! -Ouch!
-什麼？ -痛死了！
You're kidding me.
這不是真的吧？
Who is Venture Capital Partners?
夥伴創投是？
They were going to invest in us.
是預計未來會投資我們公司的企業
Isn't this pretty bad?
那不就慘了嗎？
That doesn't begin to describe it.
這哪是一個慘字能夠形容的 VCP要投資我們公司的金額
70 million?!
七千萬？
At this rate, our cash flow will run out.
這樣下去我們公司會出現資金短缺
Can we ask our other investors for a higher sum?
向其他公司請求增資如何？
Let's give it a try.
我試試看，另外
And I'll hit up every private investor I know.
我也會問問看 所有我認識的個人投資家
Thank you.
拜託你了
It happened again.
又來了
HARMONY CARE CENTER
（和諧照護中心）
Excuse me.
失陪一下
Hello?
喂？
Is this Yuri Motomiya?
請問是本宮侑里小姐嗎？
Your father's condition suddenly worsened.
你父親的病情突然惡化了
What?
什麼？
I've called the doctor as well, so please come to the center.
我們請醫生過來了，請你也盡快趕來
Boss.
社長
-Hello. -Sorry, I'll be back.
-辛苦了 -抱歉，我要出去一下
Trouble again?
又發生什麼麻煩了嗎？
Must be tough being the CEO.
當社長果然很辛苦呢
Tae-o, what's wrong?
泰晤，怎麼了？
No, it can't be.
不會吧，不要啊
This is something different. It has to be.
不會是我想的那樣，絕對不是
HARMONY CARE CENTER
（和諧照護中心）
His breath has stabilized now,
現在令尊的呼吸也穩定下來了
so there shouldn't be a problem if he continues to recover like this.
順利恢復的話 我想應該就沒有什麼問題
Thank you.
謝謝醫生
Goodbye then.
那我就離開了
Dad…
爸爸
Yuri.
侑里
What a relief.
太好了
What a huge relief.
真的太好了
Sorry about the timing.
抱歉，偏偏在這種時機出事
How is your father?
你父親的狀況如何？
They said his bronchial tube was inflamed, so he had trouble breathing.
他因為支氣管發炎而呼吸困難
It's gone down now.
但現在已經穩定下來了
I'll go to work once the paperwork is done.
手續辦完後我就回去上班
Don't worry about us.
你不用管公司的事
Stay by your father's side.
現在多陪陪你父親吧
-But-- -It's fine.
-但是… -沒事的
I'll figure it out.
我會設法解決
Thank you.
謝謝
Your power will disappear if you lock eyes for 33 seconds?
只要對視33秒就能消除能力啊？
I don't know if it's true though.
雖然不知道是真是假
But if it's true,
如果是真的
it might be my fault this happened to you.
你會變成這樣，也許是我害的
What are you saying?
別說傻話了
This isn't your fault.
這不是你的錯
But rather, this must've been so hard on you,
比起這個，你這樣獨自煩惱
worrying on your own.
一定很痛苦吧？
Hey, Yuri.
我說侑里啊
Want to test that method with me?
你要不要跟爸爸試試看那個方法？
What?
什麼？
If it goes well, you can actually get rid of your power, right?
如果順利的話 也許真的能消除那個能力
That's true, but…
雖然是那樣沒錯…
Are you scared?
你會怕嗎？
I mean…
因為…
if I really lose my power…
如果真的失去那個能力
that would mean you and I…
那我就不能再跟爸爸…
We can still talk.
我們還是能說話喔
Yesterday, I was losing consciousness,
爸爸昨天失去了意識
and I thought it was all over.
心想“這次真的要不行了”
That's when I heard it.
那時我聽到了
Your voice.
你的聲音
"Dad! Dad!"
叫著“爸爸…”
You called for me over and over.
呼喚了好幾次
Even if you lose your power,
就算你那個能力消失了
your voice will still reach me.
我還是聽得到你的聲音
I can even feel the warmth from your hand, you know.
也感受得到你的手帶來的溫暖
Let's try it, Yuri.
試試看吧，侑里
But…
不過…
It's okay.
別擔心
I…
爸爸我啊
will always be happy.
一直都很幸福喔
Now, let's give it a go.
那要開始囉
Yuri.
侑里
Don't look away, okay?
不能移開視線喔
Three…
三…
Two…
二…
One.
一
Yuri.
侑里
Open your eyes.
睜開眼吧
I want you to listen.
你先聽我說
Thank you for coming into this world as my daughter.
你能成為我的女兒 誕生在這世上，真的很感謝你
Hey, don't be like that.
等一下，不要這樣啦
You were so small when you were born.
你出生的時候真的好小
You know,
爸爸啊
I made a promise to myself when I felt your little hand,
碰到你那小小的手時，就在心裡發誓
that no matter what may come our way,
接下來不管發生什麼事
I would protect you.
都絕對要保護好你
So, on that day,
所以那一天…
I was proud that I could protect you
能夠親身保護好你
with my own two hands.
我覺得很驕傲喔
But…
可是…
That was why you…
你也因為那樣…
Yuri, I think you're misunderstanding something.
侑里啊
I feel incredibly blessed right now.
爸爸現在非常幸福喔
And then there's this.
而且還有這個
Smells nice.
好香啊
How delicious.
真好喝
Your coffee, Yuri,
侑里的咖啡
is the most delicious in the world.
是世界上最好喝的
Thank you, Yuri.
謝謝你，侑里
No.
我不要
This isn't what I want.
果然還是算了
Dad.
爸爸
This isn't what I wanted after all.
這果然不是我想要的
I'm sorry.
對不起
Dad, I'm sorry.
爸爸，對不起
I love you, Dad.
我最愛你了，爸爸
I love you too.
爸爸也最愛你了
What?!
怎麼會？
Huh?
什麼？
How?
為什麼啊？爸爸
Huh? What?
什麼？奇怪
Can you hear me?
你該不會聽得到吧？
I hear you. I hear you, Dad.
我聽得到，能聽見你的聲音，爸爸
Huh? Why?
怪了，這是為什麼呢？
Did we mess up?
失敗了嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道
I'm not sure.
雖然不清楚
But I'm so glad.
但是太好了
What a relief.
幸好還是能聽見
I'm so relieved.
真的太好了
Huh?
奇怪
Does this mean the picture book was just a coincidence?
所以那本繪本的內容 果然只是碰巧一樣？
Of course it was. It's just a picture book.
那是當然的啊，畢竟就只是繪本
Why did we believe that it was 33 seconds?
我怎麼會相信 “對視33秒”的方法呢？
Oh, jeez.
什麼嘛，真是的
I tried so hard to not blink.
爸爸還努力地忍著沒眨眼呢
Sorry.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
對不起
I'm so hungry now.
肚子好餓啊
Tae-o?
泰晤？
Why are you here?
你怎麼在這？
Welcome home. Is your father okay?
你回來啦，爸爸還好嗎？
Yeah.
他很好
He's fine now.
已經沒事了
What a relief.
那我就放心了
I'm sorry I worried you.
對不起，讓你擔心了
Not at all.
沒關係
Um, did you have dinner, by chance?
那個，你吃飯了嗎？
Hm?
嗯？
Delivery's here.
我來送外賣
Enjoy.
請用
Omurice?
蛋包飯？
Since it's your favorite.
因為這是你最喜歡吃的
Thank you.
謝謝
Delicious food
吃美味的料理
is the best way to get energized.
是最棒的能量補給
That's why
所以我啊
I always make sure to eat on both good and bad days.
不管是開心的日子 還是悲傷的日子都一定會吃飯
If you do that, you'll eventually get to enjoy the food one day.
這樣總有一天 能美味享用的日子就會到來
Enjoy.
請享用吧
Yes, thanks for the food.
謝謝你，我要開動了
It's delicious.
太好吃了
Of course. I made it.
當然好吃，因為是我做的啊
Time to eat.
我要開動了
Tastes better eating with you.
一起吃感覺更好吃了呢
Hey, Tae-o.
泰晤
Just so you know,
其實啊
my father got in an accident a long time ago.
我爸爸以前出了意外
He's been bedridden ever since.
從那時候開始，他就一直臥床不起
Even so,
但是呢
he's still the same.
他卻一點都沒變
He's kind
不但溫柔
and positive.
還很樂觀
That's why
所以我呢
I've always loved
一直都很喜歡
my dad.
那樣的爸爸
It's wonderful how much you cherish your family.
重視家人的侑里小姐很棒
Do you feel energized?
有成功補給能量嗎？
Yes.
有
Get energized.
能量補給
Get energized!
能量補給！
Energized!
補給！
Energized.
補給
I'll bring some dressing.
我去拿沙拉醬
Professor.
老師
Sorry for calling you here so suddenly.
不好意思，突然把你叫來
There's something I want to tell you, Tae-o.
我有事想跟你說，泰晤
It was 12 years ago
那是12年前的事
when I was at Kiritappu Cape in Hokkaido to do fieldwork.
當時我造訪北海道的霧多布岬 做實地考察
I saw a fishing boat accident.
我目擊了某艘漁船遭遇意外
To save the sea otters,
那時為了救海獺
Yuri Motomiya jumped into the ocean.
而跳入海裡的人就是本宮侑里小姐
Yuri?
侑里小姐嗎？
Yes.
對
However,
但是呢
Ms. Motomiya looked as if she were about to drown,
為了救起差點溺死的本宮小姐 她的父親卻出事了
I couldn't stop thinking about those two.
我非常在意那兩人的事情
Hello.
幸會
I am an endangered species researcher at Sochi University.
我在創智大學研究瀕臨絕種的動物
My name is Iiyama.
名叫飯山
The sea otters Ms. Motomiya tried to save were successfully rescued.
本宮小姐想救的那隻海獺
I sincerely thank you both.
真的非常感謝你們
However,
只不過啊
her father was no longer able to speak.
他父親已經變得連話都沒辦法講
I was concerned for him,
我很關心他的病情
so I would visit the hospital from time to time.
從那之後，也會不時去探望他
That's why I know of Yuri Motomiya from afar.
所以我也算單方面認識本宮侑里小姐
I think your girlfriend is incredibly heroic.
我認為你的女友是位非常勇敢
A wonderful person with a kind heart.
而且心地善良的出色女性
However,
但是她啊
she is harboring a secret.
有著你還不知道的祕密
Tae-o.
泰晤
Please…
這是…
think of this as a request from your father.
我以父親的身分拜託你，請你聽我說
Your girlfriend, Motomiya Yuri…
請你跟她，跟本宮侑里小姐…
Please break up with her.
分手吧
Please keep us in mind if another opportunity arises.
如果下次還有機會，請再考慮看看
Thank you. Goodbye.
好的，再見
THE REPUBLIC OF KOREA
（大韓民國）
Hello?
喂？
Is this Hanaoka from Dolce &amp; Chocolat.?
請問是朵契與巧克力的花岡先生嗎？
Yes, this is he.
是的，我是
This is Min. We met at Lake Akan, Hokkaido during the gathering.
我是和你在北海道阿寒湖的 交流會上見過面的閔
Ms. Min.
閔小姐
It's great hearing from you.
那時感謝你的捧場
Actually, I saw the news about VCP and thought of you.
其實我看了VCP的新聞後 有點在意你們的狀況
If you're okay with it, I'd like to be of help.
如果不嫌棄的話，我願意提供幫助
Really?
真的嗎？
Yes.
是的
Your company's work piqued my interest.
因為我對你們公司的業務很有興趣
I'd like to speak with you in person.
希望能見個面聊一聊
I'll be in Japan next week.
我下週剛好要去日本
Thank you. I'd love to meet you.
非常感謝你，請務必和我們見面
I'll be in touch.
我會再聯絡你
Dad, how are you feeling?
爸爸，你還好嗎？
Did you have a visitor? Someone you know?
有人來過嗎？是你認識的人？
Yuri.
侑里
Take a seat.
你坐下吧
Actually, I want to talk to you about that man.
其實我有話要跟你說 是關於那個人的事情
Hm?
什麼？
It's been a while. It's Iiyama.
好久不見，我是飯山
You can hear me, correct?
你聽得到吧？
If you can hear my voice,
如果你聽得到我的聲音
could you give me a response by blinking?
可以請你眨一下眼回答我嗎？
Thank you.
謝謝你
I actually wanted to ask you something.
其實我有件事想跟本宮先生商量
It's about your daughter,
我想來談談關於令媛
Yuri Motomiya,
本宮侑里小姐
and her secret power.
所擁有的祕密能力
What?
什麼？
It can't be.
這是怎麼回事？
How does he know?
他為什麼會知道？
In the past,
之前啊
I realized something
我看到你和女兒
when you and your daughter were talking.
在這裡對話的樣子後發現
She…
她聽得到…
can hear people's thoughts.
別人內心的聲音
Am I right?
對吧？
So, she really can.
果然如我所料
Actually,
事實上，還有一個人知道
there's one more person who knows her secret.
除了我以外，還有一人知道她的祕密
This person's name is…
那個人的名字就是…
Yun Tae-o.
尹泰晤
Her boyfriend.
就是她的戀人
First, please read this picture book.
你先讀一下這繪本
There's no need.
我不需要讀
Tae-o.
泰晤
Could it be
你該不會…
that you already know her secret?
早就知道她的祕密了？
Yes, I know.
對，我知道
But…
但是…
I've made my choice.
我已經決定了
I…
我…
will always love
會繼續愛著
Yuri.
侑里小姐
Are you prepared…
你做好…
for what's to come?
覺悟了嗎？
You do know
你曉得…
how this book ends, right?
這繪本的結局對吧？
Professor.
老師
You know,
我不要緊的
I'm Yun Tae-o.
畢竟我可是尹泰晤
Subtitle translation by: Chul Woong Kim
字幕翻譯：黃可涵
My Yuri.
侑里，我的侑里小姐
Matching pajamas?
情侶睡衣？
I love how things are now the most.
我最喜歡的是現在的樣子
Can you hear my thoughts?
能聽到我的聲音？
I don't want them to meet the same fate.
我不希望他們倆走上相同的命運
I truly love you, Yuri.
我真的非常喜歡侑里小姐喔